Guide to the Henry Noble MacCracken Papers, 1907 - circa 1968
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- SERIES III. FACULTY, 1914-1945
  - FACULTY, 1936-1939
    - Music, 1936-1939
      - Appointments (Folder 43.87)
      - Appointments (Folder 43.88)
    - Philosophy, 1936-1939
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.1)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.2)
      - Applications and Recommendations A - H (Folder 44.3)
      - Applications and Recommendations A - H (Folder 44.4)
      - Applications and Recommendations J - Z (Folder 44.5)
      - Applications and Recommendations J - Z (Folder 44.6)
      - Applications and Recommendations J - Z (Folder 44.7)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.8)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.9)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.10)
      - Conferences (Folder 44.11)
      - Officers (Folder 44.12)
      - Committee on Moritz Geiger Memorial Service (Folder 44.13)
      - Officers (Folder 44.14)
      - Officers (Folder 44.15)
    - Physical Education, 1936-1939
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.16)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.17)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.18)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.19)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.20)
      - Conferences (Folder 44.21)
      - Conferences (Folder 44.22)
      - Officers (Folder 44.23)
      - Officers (Folder 44.24)
      - Officers (Folder 44.25)
    - Physics, 1936-1939
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.26)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.27)
      - Officers (Folder 44.28)
      - Officers (Folder 44.29)
      - Officers (Folder 44.30)
    - Physiology, 1936-1939
      - Appointments (Folder 44.31)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.32)
      - Officers (Folder 44.33)
      - Officers (Folder 44.34)
      - Officers (Folder 44.35)
    - Political Science, 1936-1939
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.36)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.37)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.38)
      - Conferences (Folder 44.39)
      - Officers (Folder 44.40)
      - Officers (Folder 44.41)
      - Officers (Folder 44.42)
      - Officers (Folder 44.43)
    - Psychology, 1936-1939
      - Appointments (Folder 44.44)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.45)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.46)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.47)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.48)
      - Conferences (Folder 44.49)
      - Officers (Folder 44.50)
      - Officers (Folder 44.51)
      - Officers (Folder 44.52)
    - Religion, 1936-1939
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.53)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.54)
      - Conferences (Folder 44.55)
      - Officers (Folder 44.56)
      - Officers (Folder 44.57)
    - Russian, 1936-1939
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.58)
      - Officers (Folder 44.59)
      - Officers (Folder 44.60)
    - Spanish, 1936-1939
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.61)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.62)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.63)
      - Officers (Folder 44.64)
      - Officers (Folder 44.65)
    - Warden, 1936-1939
      - Officers (Folder 44.66)
      - Officers (Folder 44.67)
      - Officers (Folder 44.68)
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 44.69)
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 44.70)
    - Zoology, 1936-1939
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.71)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.72)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 44.73)
      - Appointments (Folder 44.74)
      - Conferences (Folder 44.75)
      - Officers (Folder 44.76)
      - Officers (Folder 44.77)
  - FACULTY, 1939-1940
    - Committees, 1939-1940
      - Faculty - Miscellaneous (Folder 45.1)
      - Chairmen of Departments (Folder 45.2)
      - Faculty Science Club (Folder 45.3)
      - Secretary of the Faculty (Folder 45.4)
      - Advisory Committee (Folder 45.5)
      - Faculty Committee of Conference (Folder 45.6)
      - Committee on Commencement (Folder 45.7)
      - Committee on Committees (Folder 45.8)
      - Committee on Conservation of American Landscape (Folder 45.9)
      - Committee on Convocation (Folder 45.10)
      - Curriculum Committee (Folder 45.11)
      - Committee on Elections (Folder 45.12)
      - Committee on Faculty Procedure (Folder 45.13)
      - Committee on Films (Folder 45.14)
      - Founder's Day Committee (Folder 45.15)
      - Committee on Graduate Study (Folder 45.16)
      - Joint Committee (Folder 45.17)
      - Library Committee (Folder 45.18)
      - Committee on Low-Cost Housing (Folder 45.19)
      - Committee on Marking System (Folder 45.20)
      - Committee on Refugee Scholars (Folder 45.21)
      - Committee on Refugee Scholars (Folder 45.22)
      - Faculty Committee on Research (Folder 45.23)
      - Schedule Committee (Folder 45.24)
      - Committee on Scholarship (Folder 45.25)
      - Committee to Study Teaching Methods (Folder 45.26)
      - Student Records Committee (Folder 45.27)
      - Committee on Swift Hall (Folder 45.28)
      - Committee on Vassar Journal of Undergraduate Study (Folder 45.29)
    - Anthropology, 1939-1940
      - Appointments (Folder 45.30)
      - Officers (Folder 45.31)
      - Archeological Projects [includes correspondence re: Mary Butler and excavations at West Point] (Folder 45.32)
    - Art, 1939-1940
      - Appointments (Folder 45.33)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.34)
      - Officers (Folder 45.35)
    - Astronomy, 1939-1940
      - Officers (Folder 45.36)
      - Applications (Folder 45.37)
    - Botany, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.38)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.39)
      - Officers (Folder 45.40)
    - Chemistry, 1939-1940
      - Appointments (Folder 45.41)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.42)
      - Officers (Folder 45.43)
    - Child Study, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.44)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.45)
      - Conferences (Folder 45.46)
      - Officers (Folder 45.47)
    - Dean, 1939-1940
      - Officers - Committee on Admission (Folder 45.48)
      - Appointments - Committee on Admission (Folder 45.49)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.50)
      - Conferences (Folder 45.51)
      - Officers (Folder 45.52)
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 45.53)
    - Drama, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.54)
      - Officers (Folder 45.55)
    - Economics, 1939-1940
      - Appointments (Folder 45.56)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.57)
      - Officers (Folder 45.58)
    - English, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.59)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.60)
      - Officers (Folder 45.61)
    - Euthenics, 1939-1940
      - Institute of Euthenics (Folder 45.62)
    - French, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.63)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.64)
      - Officers (Folder 45.65)
    - Geology, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.66)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.67)
    - German, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.68)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.69)
      - Officers (Folder 45.70)
    - Greek, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.71)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.72)
      - Officers (Folder 45.73)
    - Health, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.74)
      - Officers (Folder 45.75)
    - History, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.76)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.77)
      - Officers (Folder 45.78)
    - Italian, 1939-1940
      - Officers (Folder 45.79)
    - Latin, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.80)
      - Officers (Folder 45.81)
    - Library, 1939-1940
      - Appointments (Folder 45.82)
      - Officers (Folder 45.83)
    - Mathematics, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.84)
      - Officers (Folder 45.85)
    - Music, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.86)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.87)
      - Officers (Folder 45.88)
    - Philosophy, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 45.89)
      - Appointments (Folder 45.90)
      - Officers (Folder 45.91)
    - Physical Education, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.1)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.2)
      - Officers (Folder 46.3)
    - Physics, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.4)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.5)
      - Officers (Folder 46.6)
    - Physiology, 1939-1940
      - Appointments (Folder 46.7)
      - Officers (Folder 46.8)
    - Political Science, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.9)
      - Officers (Folder 46.10)
    - Psychology, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.11)
      - Officers (Folder 46.12)
    - Religion, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.13)
      - Officers (Folder 46.14)
    - Russian, 1939-1940
      - Officers (Folder 46.15)
    - Spanish, 1939-1940
      - Conferences (Folder 46.16)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.17)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.18)
      - Officers (Folder 46.19)
    - Warden, 1939-1940
      - Officers (Folder 46.20)
      - Conferences (Folder 46.21)
    - Zoology, 1939-1940
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.22)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.23)
      - Officers (Folder 46.24)
      - Conferences (Folder 46.25)
      - Officers (Folder 46.26)
  - FACULTY, Aug 1940 - July 1941
    - Anthropology, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Officers (Folder 46.27)
    - Art, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.28)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.29)
      - Officers (Folder 46.30)
    - Astronomy, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Appointments (Folder 46.31)
      - Officers (Folder 46.32)
    - Botany, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Officers (Folder 46.33)
    - Chemistry, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.34)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.35)
      - Officers (Folder 46.36)
    - Child Study, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Appointments (Folder 46.37)
      - Officers (Folder 46.38)
    - Dean, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Appointments (Folder 46.39)
      - Conferences (Folder 46.40)
      - Officers (Folder 46.41)
      - Count of Courses, 1939-1940 (Folder 46.42)
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 46.43)
    - Drama, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.44)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.45)
      - Officers (Folder 46.46)
    - Economics, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.47)
      - Conferences (Folder 46.48)
      - Officers (Folder 46.49)
    - English, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.50)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.51)
      - Conferences (Folder 46.52)
      - Memorial for Mary Maccoll (Folder 46.53)
      - Officers (Folder 46.54)
    - Euthenics, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Officers (Folder 46.55)
      - Summer Institute of Euthenics (Folder 46.56)
    - French, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.57)
      - Officers (Folder 46.58)
    - Geography, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.59)
      - Officers (Folder 46.60)
    - Geology, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Appointments (Folder 46.61)
      - Officers (Folder 46.62)
    - German, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.63)
      - Conferences (Folder 46.64)
      - Officers (Folder 46.65)
    - Greek, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.66)
      - Officers (Folder 46.67)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.68)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.69)
      - Officers (Folder 46.70)
    - History, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.71)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.72)
      - Officers (Folder 46.73)
    - Italian, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.74)
    - Latin, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.75)
      - Officers (Folder 46.76)
    - Library, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.77)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.78)
      - Officers (Folder 46.79)
    - Mathematics, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.80)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.81)
      - Officers (Folder 46.82)
    - Music, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Conferences (Folder 46.83)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.84)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.85)
      - Officers (Folder 46.86)
    - Philosophy, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.87)
      - Officers (Folder 46.88)
    - Physical Education, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.89)
      - Officers (Folder 46.90)
    - Physics, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Appointments (Folder 46.91)
      - Conferences (Folder 46.92)
      - Officers (Folder 46.93)
    - Physiology, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Appointments (Folder 46.94)
      - Officers (Folder 46.95)
    - Political Science, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.96)
      - Officers (Folder 46.97)
    - Psychology, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 46.98)
      - Appointments (Folder 46.99)
    - Religion, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Officers (Folder 46.100)
    - Russian, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Officers (Folder 46.101)
    - Spanish, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.1)
      - Officers (Folder 47.2)
      - Appointments (Folder 47.3)
    - Warden, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.4)
      - Appointments (Folder 47.5)
      - Officers (Folder 47.6)
    - Zoology, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.7)
      - Appointments (Folder 47.8)
      - Officers (Folder 47.9)
    - Faculty Committees, Aug 1940 - July 1941
      - Committee on Academic Statute (Folder 47.10)
      - Officers - Committee on Admission (Folder 47.11)
      - Secretary of the Faculty (Folder 47.12)
      - Advisory Committee (Folder 47.13)
      - Committee on Commencement (Folder 47.14)
      - Committee on Committees (Folder 47.15)
      - Committee on Conference (Folder 47.16)
      - Committee on Convocation (Folder 47.17)
      - Committee on Cooperative Houses (Folder 47.18)
      - Curriculum Committee (Folder 47.19)
      - Emergency Committee (Folder 47.20)
      - Committee on Faculty Procedure (Folder 47.21)
      - Film Committee (Folder 47.22)
      - Founder's Day Committee (Folder 47.23)
      - Committee on Graduate Study (Folder 47.24)
      - Joint Committee (Folder 47.25)
      - Committee on Journal of Undergraduate Studies (Folder 47.26)
      - Library Committee (Folder 47.27)
      - Committee on Pre-medical Work (Folder 47.28)
      - Radio Workshop Committee (Folder 47.29)
      - Committee on Refugee Scholars (Folder 47.30)
      - Faculty Committee on Research (Folder 47.31)
      - Schedule Committee (Folder 47.32)
      - Committee on Scholarships (Folder 47.33)
      - Committee on Student Records (Folder 47.34)
      - Committee on Survey of Academic Buildings (Folder 47.35)
      - Committee on Swift Hall (Folder 47.36)
      - Committee on Teacher Training Law (Folder 47.37)
      - Officers - Dean (Folder 47.38)
      - Count of Courses, 1942-1943 (Folder 47.39)
      - Count of Courses (Folder 47.40)
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 47.41)
      - Officers - Committee on admission (Folder 47.42)
      - Officers - Warden (Folder 47.43)
      - Board of Residents (Folder 47.44)
  - FACULTY, 1941-1943
    - Library, 1941-1943
      - Appointments (Folder 47.45)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.46)
      - Officers (Folder 47.47)
    - Anthropology, 1941-1943
      - Officers (Folder 47.48)
      - Survey Part 1 (Folder 47.49)
      - Survey Part 2 (Folder 47.50)
    - Art, 1941-1943
      - Appointments (Folder 47.51)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.52)
      - Officers (Folder 47.53)
    - Astronomy, 1941-1943
      - Appointments (Folder 47.54)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.55)
      - Officers (Folder 47.56)
    - Chemistry, 1941-1943
      - Appointments (Folder 47.57)
      - Officers (Folder 47.58)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.59)
    - Child Study, 1941-1943
      - Appointments (Folder 47.60)
      - Officers (Folder 47.61)
      - Child Study Material for the Curriculum Committee and Professors Fisher and Lanier (Folder 47.62)
      - Child Study Material for the Curriculum Committee and Professors Fisher and Lanier (Folder 47.63)
    - Drama, 1941-1943
      - Appointments (Folder 47.64)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.65)
      - Officers (Folder 47.66)
    - Economics, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.67)
      - Appointments (Folder 47.68)
      - Officers (Folder 47.69)
      - Officers (Folder 47.70)
    - English, 1941-1943
      - Appointments (Folder 47.71)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.72)
      - Officers (Folder 47.73)
    - Euthenics, 1941-1943
      - Officers (Folder 47.74)
      - Summer Institute of Euthenics (Folder 47.75)
    - French, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 47.76)
      - Officers (Folder 47.77)
    - Geography, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.1)
      - Officers (Folder 48.2)
    - Geology, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.3)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.4)
      - Officers (Folder 48.5)
    - German, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.6)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.7)
      - Officers (Folder 48.8)
    - Greek, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.9)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.10)
      - Officers (Folder 48.11)
    - Health, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.12)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.13)
      - Consulting Psychiatrist (Folder 48.14)
      - Officers (Folder 48.15)
    - History, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.16)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.17)
      - Officers (Folder 48.18)
    - Italian, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.19)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.20)
      - Officers (Folder 48.21)
    - Latin, 1941-1943
      - Appointments (Folder 48.22)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.23)
      - Officers (Folder 48.24)
    - Mathematics, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.25)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.26)
      - Officers (Folder 48.27)
    - Music, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.28)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.29)
      - Officers (Folder 48.30)
      - Officers (Folder 48.31)
    - Philosophy, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.32)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.33)
      - Officers (Folder 48.34)
    - Physical Education, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.35)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.36)
      - Officers (Folder 48.37)
    - Physics, 1941-1943
      - Memorial to Miss Wick (Folder 48.38)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.39)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.40)
      - Officers (Folder 48.41)
    - Physiology, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.42)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.43)
      - Officers (Folder 48.44)
    - Plant Science, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.45)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.46)
      - Officers (Folder 48.47)
    - Political Science, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.48)
      - Officers (Folder 48.49)
    - Psychology, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.50)
      - Officers (Folder 48.51)
      - Officers (Folder 48.52)
    - Religion, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.53)
      - Officers (Folder 48.54)
    - Russian, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.55)
      - Officers (Folder 48.56)
    - Spanish, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.57)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.58)
      - Officers (Folder 48.59)
    - Zoology, 1941-1943
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 48.60)
      - Appointments (Folder 48.61)
      - Officers (Folder 48.62)
    - Committees, 1941-1943
      - Faculty Club (Folder 48.63)
      - Faculty - General (Folder 48.64)
      - Chairmen of Departments (Folder 48.65)
      - Committee on Academic Statute (Folder 48.66)
      - Faculty Committee to Study Acceleration (Joint comm. w/trustees) (Folder 48.67)
      - Advisory Committee (Folder 48.68)
      - Committee on Committees (Folder 48.69)
      - Committee on Conferences (Folder 48.70)
      - Conservation Committee (Folder 48.71)
      - Committee on Displaced Scholars (Folder 48.72)
      - Curriculum Committee (Folder 48.73)
      - Curriculum Committee (Folder 48.74)
      - Committee on Faculty Procedure (Folder 48.75)
      - Committee on Fellowships and Graduate Study (Folder 48.76)
      - Film Committee (Folder 48.77)
      - Joint Committee (Folder 48.78)
      - Committee on Vassar Journal of Undergraduate Studies (Folder 48.79)
      - Committee on Key Center (Folder 48.80)
      - Committee on Library (Folder 48.81)
      - Radio Workshop Committee (Folder 48.82)
      - Committee on Plans for Training Reconstruction Workers (Folder 48.83)
      - Faculty Committee on Research (Folder 48.84)
      - Subcommittee on Residence (Folder 48.85)
      - Scholarship Committee (Folder 48.86)
      - Committee on Self-Help (Folder 48.87)
      - Committee on Teacher Education (Folder 48.88)
      - Budget (Folder 48.89)
  - FACULTY, 1943-1945
    - Dean, 1943-1945
      - Vocational Bureau (Folder 49.1)
      - Committee on Admissions (Folder 49.2)
      - Count of Courses (Folder 49.3)
      - Count of Courses (Folder 49.4)
      - Officers - Dean (Folder 49.5)
      - Assistant Dean (Folder 49.6)
    - Warden, 1943-1945
      - Board of Residents (Folder 49.7)
      - Appointments (Folder 49.8)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 49.9)
      - Officers (Folder 49.10)
      - Officers (Folder 49.11)
    - Library, 1943-1945
      - Miss Fay's Survey of Vassar College Library (Folder 49.12)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 49.13)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 49.14)
      - Appointments (Folder 49.15)
      - Officers (Folder 49.16)
      - Officers (Folder 49.17)
    - Anthropology, 1943-1945
      - Officers (Folder 49.18)
    - Art, 1943-1945
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 49.19)
      - Appointments (Folder 49.20)
      - Officers (Folder 49.21)
      - Officers (Folder 49.22)
    - Astronomy, 1943-1945
      - Officers (Folder 49.23)
    - Chemistry, 1943-1945
      - Appointments (Folder 49.24)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 49.25)
      - Officers (Folder 49.26)
    - Child Study, 1943-1945
      - Appointments (Folder 49.27)
      - Officers (Folder 49.28)
    - Drama, 1943-1945
      - Appointments (Folder 49.29)
      - Applications and Recommendations (Folder 49.30)
      - Officers (Folder 49.31)
    - Economics, 1943-1945